<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Deep Space Scouting App</string>

    <string name="toolbar_title">@string/app_name</string>

    <string name="title_activity_endgame">Endgame</string>

    <!--Popup strings-->
    <string name="bluetooth_setup_title">Connect over Bluetooth</string>

    <string name="data_errors_title">Your data have errors.</string>

    <string name="not_connected_title">Bluetooth failed to connect.</string>
    <string name="not_connected_prompt">This device is not connected to Bluetooth. The data you submit will be stored locally, but not sent to the scouting laptop.\nWould you like try to reconnect now?</string>

    <string name="bluetooth_connected_title">Bluetooth Connected</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_connected_prompt">Bluetooth has successfully connected to %1$s</string>

    <string name="bluetooth_send_failed_title">Bluetooth submission failed.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_send_failed_prompt">Please talk to Carter or another scouting leader</string>

    <string name="bluetooth_connect_error_title">Bluetooth Error</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_connect_error_prompt">An error occurred connecting to Bluetooth.\nPlease check that Bluetooth is enabled on this device, that the server is running on the scouting computer, and that you have selected that computer from the dropdown. Then try connecting again by clicking the Bluetooth icon in the top corner.\nIf errors persist, please get Carter for help.</string>

    <string name="info_popup_button">Okay</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_popup_connect_button">Connect</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_warning_ignore_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="popup_cancel_button">Cancel</string>


    <!--Help Popups-->
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>

    <string name="help_appwide">Welcome to the 449 Blair Robot Project Deep Space Scouting App!\n\nFor each match, you will be assigned a team to scout. Watch this robot closely throughout the match, and record what they do.\nOn each page, fill out the fields, and then move on with the navigation buttons at the bottom. You can go pack to a previous page to edit that data.\n\nWhen you are done, hit the submit button.\nIf you realise you entered something wrong after submitting, you can edit it. Hit the edit icon at the top of the screen, select the match, and hit edit. Any data you entered for the next match will be preserved for when you finish editing.\n\nOn many questions you will see a ? icon. Click this to get more information about that field\nIf you need more help with something, don\'t hesitate to ask a scouting leader.</string>

    <string name="help_default">Please talk to a scouting leader for help.</string>
    <string name="help_noshow">If the team\'s robot is not on the field for this match, select the box.</string>
    <string name="help_matchNum">Record the match number.\nIf this is a rematch, just put the match number that it is a rematch for.</string>
    <string name="help_placement">Each time the robot you are watching places a game piece, record it here.\nClick a circle once to place a hatch, twice for a cargo, and three times if they place both. A fourth click will clear it.\n\nIt does not matter which rocket is which, or which side of the cargo ship is which.\n\nPlease only record pieces placed by YOUR robot, and INCLUDE those placed in the Sandstorm period.\n\nIf the robot places multiple cargo in one location, don\'t record it.</string>
    <string name="help_drop">Each time your robot drops a game piece that they had previously been holding, for any reason (including if they are trying to place it and miss), please record it here by clicking the + button.</string>
    <string name="help_startingLevel">What HAB level did the robot start on?\nLevel 1: the low base with a small ramp\nLevel 2: the two short platforms about 6 inches above level 1.\nIf the robot is a no show, you can leave this blank (or just put 1).</string>
    <string name="help_preload">What game element did the robot start the match with?</string>
    <string name="help_crossedLine">If the robot moved and made it off of the HAB platform onto the carpet DURING SANDSTORM, check this box.\n(You may be familiar with \'Moved Forward\' or \'Crossed Line\' from past games - this is the same idea)</string>
    <string name="help_placedPreloaded">If the robot successfully placed their preloaded game piece DURING SANDSTORM check this box.</string>
    <string name="help_doubleAuto">If the robot picked up and placed another game piece DURING SANDSTORM select the game piece that they placed. Otherwise, select "No" (or leave the item blank).</string>
    <string name="help_levelAttempted">What HAB level did they ATTEMPT to climb to?\n\nLevel 1: bottom platform\nLevel 2: two mid-level platforms (~6in)\nLevel 3: highest platform (between the two level 2 platforms)\n\nDo your best to judge intent, if they doing something that looked like it was supposed to get them up, that\'s an attempt. If you aren\'t sure, don\'t hesitate to ask a scouting lead.</string>
    <string name="help_climbSuccess">Did the robot climb successfully? A successful climb has the robot reach and stay at the level they attempted. If no climb was attempted, simply put N/A (or leave it blank). A level 1 climb (the base platform) does count as a climb.</string>
    <string name="help_levelReached">At the end of the match, what level was the robot at? (1 is the bottom platform, 2 is either of the two middle platforms, 3 is the highest platform)\nTo be a legal climb, the robot must:\n - be fully supported only by things at or above the level they have climbed to\n - have bumpers above that level.\n - have left the HAB at some point in the match\n\nIf, for example, a robot tries a level 3 climb, but they are supported by the side of the platform, above the height of level 2, this would count as a level 2 climb.</string>
    <string name="help_climbTime">If the robot completed a level 2 or 3 climb, approximately how long did they spend, from the time they drove onto level 1 to the time they were stable and supported only by the level they are climbing to, with bumpers above that level.\nYou can use the timer to help count, or you can manually adjust the value by dragging it up or down.</string>
    <string name="help_dead">Alive: the robot was enabled, moving, and mostly functional for most of the match.\n\nBroken: robot was moving, but something is wrong. There are parts of their robot that are clearly broken.\n\nHalf dead: Dead for a significant portion of the match (think 35–70%).\n\nDead: Robot is just sitting on the field unable to move.</string>
    <string name="help_defense">If the robot attempted defense, how good was it?\n\n - Good defense would effectively prevent a robot from scoring many game pieces, or greatly decrease their cycle time (and doesn\'t cause lots of fouls).\n - \'Meh\' defense has a small impact on the game. It hinders the opponent a little bit, but they are able to work around the defender.\n - Bad defense is completely useless, and doesn\'t have any impact on the opponents, or it results in many fouls, or is interfering with alliance partners.\n\nThis is a subjective field, just put whatever you feel is best. Don\'t worry about choosing the \'correct\' option, we have qualitative scouting for more accurate/detailed defense data.</string>

</resources>
